https://www.howardmiller.com/webapp/wcs/stores/servlet/en/howardmiller/howard-miller-privacy-policy

Message Dialog
Close
Display Update Message
Product Comparison
The maximum number of products that can be compared is 4. Please refine your selection.
OK
Your session is about to timeout due to inactivity.
Click OK to extend your time for an additional 0 minutes.
OK
This item has been successfully added to your list.
Compare
Howard Miller Sounds of the Season Silver Table Clock 645687
Privacy Policy
Howard Miller Internet Privacy Policy:
Howard Miller recognizes the privacy concerns of visitors to it’s sites on the Internet. Specifically, Howard Miller recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about the visitors to Howard Miller’s Web site. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information is automatically collected from visitors to Howard Miller’s sites, unless you provide Howard Miller that information voluntarily.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
Howard Miller gathers information about Web site visitors to improve the caliber of online information and services offered. There are two forms of data that Howard Miller collects: site visitor data and personal information voluntarily provided to Howard Miller by site visitors.
SITE VISITOR DATA
Howard Miller routinely gathers data on Web site activity, such as how many people visit the site, the pages they visit, etc. Site visitor data is:
Collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, which means no personal information is associated with this data.
Gathered through the use of Web server logs and cookies. A Web server log is a file where Web site activity is stored. A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web site sends to a visitor’s computer, which is stored on the visitor’s hard drive. Howard Miller uses cookies to track repeat visits, track usage patterns and better serve you. The cookie does not extract personal information about you. Most browsers provide a simple procedure to reject cookies or enable you to control whether you want to receive cookies through prior notification.
Shared among the Howard Miller family of companies to improve site content and overall service.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
Howard Miller collects personal information submitted from site visitors, such as a visitor’s name, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc. Personal information is collected only when site visitors voluntarily provide it. Personal information, excluding credit card information, collected from the Howard Miller Store may be disclosed to a Howard Miller dealer as necessary or appropriate to process any orders. Howard Miller does not collect credit card information. Portions of the Howard Miller web site may require registration and log-in processes in which you select a user ID and password (collectively, the “Password”). You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any Password. All activities that occur using your Password are your responsibility, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify Howard Miller of any unauthorized use of your Password or accounts.
E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS
Any comments or questions sent via e-mail to Howard Miller might be shared with our customer service representatives, independent sales representatives or those employees most capable of addressing your questions and concerns. Howard Miller will retain your communication until we have done our best to provide you with a complete response and then will either discard it, or, in some cases, archive it.
Please be advised that most email systems do not provide a means for completely secure and private communications. Non-encrypted email communications may be accessed and viewed by others while in transit to or from Howard Miller. For that reason, do not use e-mail to communicate information to Howard Miller that you consider to be confidential.
Howard Miller will not sell, trade or otherwise disclose personal information or email communication outside the Howard Miller family of companies unless required to do so by legal, judicial or governmental proceedings, or unless required to do so in accordance with any authorization you have given us.
CONSENT TO TRANSFER
Howard Miller is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using this web site or providing us with your information, you hereby consent to this transfer.
REVISIONS
Howard Miller may at any time revise this Internet Privacy Policy by updating this posting.
HOW CAN WE HELP?
Help Center
Find A Retailer
Locate A Service Center
Online Catalogs
Manuals & Warranties
Online Videos
Order Parts
Floor Clock Setup Video
Heirloom Plate
Heirloom Record & Capsule
Safety Strap
WARNING California Prop 65
×
WARNING: This product can expose you to chemicals including wood dust, styrene, or nickel, which is known to the State of California to cause cancer or birth defects or other reproductive harm. For more information, go to: www.PS65Warnings.ca.gov/furniture.
FOLLOW US TO STAY CONNECTED
© 2020 Howard Miller | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
AUTHORIZED DEALERS
Dealer Services Login
Dealer Services Registration
Non-Warranty Parts Store
Digital Image Gallery
Dealer Terms of Sale
